https://goldcoffee.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Gold Coffee Company has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site, our products and our services.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you purchase a product from www.goldcoffee.com, we ask you to provide information required to fulfill your order. You will need to provide your name, email address, phone number, shipping address, and billing address in order to process an order. We will also require you to create a username and password.
Credit Card Information
If you choose to purchase products from us, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
Web Site Use Information
We do employ cookies a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) to allow us to maintain products in your shopping cart as you explore various parts of our Web site. Cookies also allow us to know if you have visited our site before or if you are a first time visitor. This provides us with important marketing information and lets us know how we are doing at both attracting new visitors and maintaining relationships with our existing customers. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.
Cookies are required to place an online order with us. Should you wish to not accept cookies in your web browser, you may place a phone order, at 561-746-8110.
What Are Cookies?
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
As a www.goldcoffee.com customer, your email address and phone number will never be rented, sold, or provided to a third party. Occasionally, we make special offers available to our customers — promotions, sales, events, discounts, etc. You may periodically receive a newsletter e-mail from us regarding these special offers. If you do not want to receive a newsletter from us concerning special promotions, savings, events or other important information, simply use the “unsubscribe” link found in the footer of the newsletter to change your preferences. Should you have questions about how we use your information, feel free to send us a message by visiting the Contact Us section of this Web site.
Secure Online Ordering
You can shop at www.goldcoffee.com with confidence. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to accept credit cards and electronic check payments safely and securely for our customers.
The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the electronic check and credit card processing networks. See an online payments diagram  to see how it works. Gold Coffee Company has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to the highest level of integrity in dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site, our products and our services.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you purchase a product from www.goldcoffee.com, we ask you to provide information required to fulfill your order. You will need to provide your name, email address, phone number, shipping address, and billing address in order to process an order. We will also require you to create a username and password.
Credit Card Information
If you choose to purchase products from us, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services.
Email Information
If you choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
Web Site Use Information
We do employ cookies a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) to allow us to maintain products in your shopping cart as you explore various parts of our Web site. Cookies also allow us to know if you have visited our site before or if you are a first time visitor. This provides us with important marketing information and lets us know how we are doing at both attracting new visitors and maintaining relationships with our existing customers. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.
Cookies are required to place an online order with us. Should you wish to not accept cookies in your web browser, you may place a phone order, at 561-746-8110.
What Are Cookies?
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
As a www.goldcoffee.com customer, your email address and phone number will never be rented, sold, or provided to a third party. Occasionally, we make special offers available to our customers — promotions, sales, events, discounts, etc. You may periodically receive a newsletter e-mail from us regarding these special offers. If you do not want to receive a newsletter from us concerning special promotions, savings, events or other important information, simply use the “unsubscribe” link found in the footer of the newsletter to change your preferences. Should you have questions about how we use your information, feel free to send us a message by visiting the Contact Us section of this Web site.
Secure Online Ordering
You can shop at www.goldcoffee.com with confidence. We have partnered with Authorize.Net, a leading payment gateway since 1996, to accept credit cards and electronic check payments safely and securely for our customers.
The Authorize.Net Payment Gateway manages the complex routing of sensitive customer information through the electronic check and credit card processing networks. See an online payments diagram  to see how it works.The company adheres to strict industry standards for payment processing, including: • 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for secure Internet Protocol (IP) transactions. • Industry leading encryption hardware and software methods and security protocols to protect customer information. • Compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS).For additional information regarding the privacy of your sensitive cardholder data, please read the Authorize.Net Privacy Policy.
www.goldcoffee.com  is registered with the Authorize.Net Verified Merchant Seal program.
